{
    "subject": "Brian_Dannelly",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Saved!",
    "human_readable": "Brian Dannelly created Saved!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5495446920394897,
            "question": "What is the title of the movie created by Brian Dannelly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4443395435810089,
            "question": "Who created the movie Saved!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3771687150001526,
            "question": "What year was Saved! released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3752312958240509,
            "question": "Is Brian Dannelly known for directing movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22328335046768188,
            "question": "What awards or recognition has Saved! received?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21329547464847565,
            "question": "Can you name another movie directed by Brian Dannelly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19782491028308868,
            "question": "What might be a common theme explored in Saved!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19033946096897125,
            "question": "Are there any actors known for their roles in Saved!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17435777187347412,
            "question": "What makes Saved! a unique movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14232681691646576,
            "question": "What genre is the movie Saved! likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Brian Dannelly created Saved!",
            "html": "yago_10555_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes Saved! a unique movie?",
            "html": "yago_10555_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any actors known for their roles in Saved!",
            "html": "yago_10555_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be a common theme explored in Saved!",
            "html": "yago_10555_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10555_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10555_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10555_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10555_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10555_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10555_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10555_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10555_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10555_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10555_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly states that \"Brian Dannelly\u2019s film, \u2018Saved!\u2019\" and also mentions \"Director Brian Dannelly\u2019s claims his film \u201cSaved!\u201d\", indicating that Brian Dannelly created the movie Saved!."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Brian Dannelly's film \"Saved!\", including the fact that it was his first feature film and that he co-wrote it with Michael Urban. This supports the statement that Brian Dannelly created \"Saved!\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}